{"questions":[{"question":"What will be consider as Stand-alone applications","level":2,"answers":["An app that execute on a remote computer and are accessed by users from their own PCs or terminals","an app that include software control systems that control and manage hardware devices","An app that do not need to be connected to a network","An app that stand alone in the registry"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":3},{"question":"what is Scrum","level":2,"answers":["Scrum is a framework for managing work with an emphasis on software development.","scrum is a relatively linear sequential design approach for certain areas of engineering design","scrum is the process of dividing software development work into distinct phases to improve design, product management, and project management.","scrum is a description of a software system to be developed"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":1},{"question":"What is the correct order of waterfall","level":2,"answers":["Requirement,design,implementation,verification,maintence","Maintence, design, Requirement, implementation, verification","Verification, Requirement, design, Maintence, implementation","Requirement, Verification, design, implementation, maintence"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":1},{"question":"What of the following is an example of a functional requirment","level":2,"answers":["low cost ,reduced time ,no maintenance","risk of data, capacity ceiling,cost","greater control ,more security ,higher performance","lack of control ,slow speed ,lack of investment"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":3},{"question":"scenarios (examples of how a system can be used) should include:","level":2,"answers":["information about other concurrent activities","participants' system usage hours","design review","participants' professional qualifications"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":1},{"question":"SOA helps the company to deal with more than one product across more than one platform. True or False","level":2,"answers":["True","False",""],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":1},{"question":"What of the following is an example of a functional requirment","level":2,"answers":["scalability","Reliability","security","external inerfaces"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":4},{"question":"External requirements are Requirements which are a consequence of organisational policies and procedures. True or False","level":2,"answers":["True","False",""],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":1},{"question":"Review team is","level":2,"answers":["Senior project members","Senior professionals","Customer representatives","All the Answers Are Correct"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":4},{"question":"what is JSON","level":1,"answers":["evil character in movies","JavaScript Object Notation","a popular means of transferring data between servers and clients","Journalistic Stream Of News"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":3},{"question":"Peer Reviews- is one of Reviews Types","level":1,"answers":["True","False",""],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":1},{"question":"TDD Is","level":3,"answers":["is a software development process that relies on the repetition of a very short development cycle","is a format for describing streaming media communications parameters","is a description of a software system to be developed","is an agile framework for managing knowledge work"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":1},{"question":"what is WIMP","level":3,"answers":["an agile method","an sdp protocol","A gui requirement","windows, icons, menus, pointers"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":4},{"question":"Unit testing is the process of testing individual components in isolation.True or False","level":3,"answers":["False","True",""],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":2},{"question":"how many percents of the total cost of a product accrues during the maintenance phase","level":3,"answers":["90%","15%","67%","13.5%"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":1},{"question":"An example of adaptive maintenance feature is","level":3,"answers":["Client requests changes to improve product effectiveness","responses to changes in the environment in which the product operates","correct residual faults","none of the above"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":2}]}